You're the light,
you're the night
You're the colour of my blood
You're the cure, you're the pain
You're the only thing I wanna touch
Never knew that it could mean
so much, so much
You're the fear, I don't care
Cause I've never been so high
Follow me through the dark
Let me take you past the satellites
You can see the world
you brought to life, to life
So love me like you do,
la-la-love me like you do
Love me like you do,
Touch me like you do,
ta-ta-touch me like you do
What are you waiting for?
Fading in, fading out
on the edge of the paradise
Every inch of your skin is
a Holy Grail I've got to find
Only you can set my heart
on fire,
on fire, yeah
I'll let you set the pace
Cause I'm not thinking straight
My head's spinning around,
I can't see clear no more
What are you waiting for?
Love me like you do, la-la-love me
like you do (Like you do)
Love me like you do,
la-la-love me like you do
Touch me like you do,
ta-ta-touch me like you do
What are you waiting for?
Love me like you do, la-la-love me
like you do (Like you do)
like you do (Yeah)
Touch me like you do, ta-ta-touch
me like you do (Ooh ooh ooh)
What are you waiting for?
I'll let you set the pace
Cause I'm not thinking straight
My head's spinning around,
I can't see clear no more
What are you waiting for?
Love me like you do, la-la-love me
like you do
(Like you do)
Love me like you do, la-la-love
me like you do (Yeah)
Touch me like you do, ta-ta-touch
me like you do (Ooh ooh ooh)
What are you waiting for?
Love me like you do, la-la-love me
like you do
(Like you do)
Love me like you do, la-la-love me
like you do (Whoa)
Touch me like you do,
ta-ta-touch me like you do
What are you waiting for?